http://barrettsfencing.com/privacy-policy-s6.php

Privacy Policy
We understand that confidentiality is important to you and essential in our business. It is our policy that all personal information you supply to us will be considered confidential. This policy holds true no matter how we receive your personal information; over the phone, e-mail or online through this website.
We may use "cookies" on some pages of our website, simply to help us serve you better each time you return. A cookie is a small element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. The data collected from cookies helps us determine how many people visit this site and which pages they view. We use this information to better serve all visitors as we improve our site content and design. You can set your Web browser to warn you before you accept a cookie. We do not use cookies to collect any personal information.
We do collect information on the domains people visit us from. This data helps us track trends in our website traffic and as the basis for making improvements. We do not share this information with any third parties.
Our website may contain links to other sites, and we make every effort to link only to sites with content suitable for all ages.
We reserve the right at our discretion to make changes to this privacy policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes.
1023618 Ontario Inc. o/a Barrett’s Farm & Family Centre, 449 Barrett Road, Stirling, Ontario K0K 3E0
1-800-345-7303 or local 613-395-1433  | Terms of Use  |  Privacy Policy
</html
